Children of God, Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Corporal Yerimah Peter Ojoh.
I am from Edo State by birth. I reside here in Lagos.
I serve as a soldier in the Nigerian army.
Praise God.
The testimony that I have to share with you this morning
is a testimony about a liver infection.
Many people believe that a liver infection has no cure.
But Jesus has the cure.
Corporal Yerimah Ojoh. Emmanuel TV testimony.
It all happened in 2012 when my wife gave birth.
I was away on a mission in Darfur when my wife gave birth to my first son.
After giving birth, from the second day, unusual things started happening in my life.
My body changed - I could not walk, breath and even see well.
These are the things that started happening in my life.
I couldn't share this with anybody.
I was just lying in the hostel.
I was encouraged to visit the hospital for a medical check-up.
I could not go by myself, the M.R.S. on the mission assisted me.
The doctors could not detect the cause and referred me to our Level 1 hospital in Nyala,
which is the transit camp for all military staff in Darfur.
They carried out some medical examinations and could not detect what it was and referred me again,
to Pakistan Military Hospital, which is at Level 3.
I couldn't walk so I was assisted to reach there.
It was there where they carried out some medical tests about my life.
What you are seeing here are not school certificates but certificates of life.
Praise the Lord.
Please, can you help me.
God bless you.
The first one on the board indicates all the blood functions,
and they discovered that there was no problem.
They conducted a test on the liver. I didn't know then that I had a liver problem.
They detected that I had a liver infection.
It had risen from a normal number up to 80. If it had went up from 80 to 90, that would have been fatal.
The doctor's report confirmed that I could not walk, had severe headaches, pains, dizziness and could not stand.
They had to refer me to a place where they could refer me back to my country.
I and another soldier had that problem.
We were told that by Monday, the two of us would be referred to Nigeria.
That there was no cure for this kind of sickness.
On Sunday, my colleague who is now retired -
I believe wherever he is now he is watching Emmanuel TV because he is an Emmanuel TV partner -
he said they should bring me to the screen
because he had a laptop in the hostel on which he was watching the LIVE service.
He said they should call me and assist me to be there
as the Man of God was about to pray for the whole nation.
He wanted me to join them and lay my hand on the screen as he knew that something would happen.
The Man of God began praying. He said, "Wherever you are now, touch the screen, distance is not a barrier.
Connect your faith with mine. Whatever problem you have, Jesus knows about it".
Corporal Yerimah Ojoh. Emmanuel TV testimony.
I touched the screen and he then mentioned my problem.
He said, "I speak to your liver, bones and kidneys.
Whatsoever pain you have, I command the pain out!"
I said "Amen". They assisted me to touch the screen, then after the prayer they assisted me back to my bed.
During the night, something happened.
I was sleeping. Then, I heard a voice, an echoing voice saying, "My son, stand up!"
I woke up from my body, part of me was still lying down. I rose up and looked at myself.
I said, "Ah, what kind of magic is this?" because I was still seeing part of myself lying down.
He said, "I created you without a problem. Those bodies you are seeing here..." - I was seeing two bodies.
I was seeing myself lying down on one side and another replica of myself lying down next to that one.
He said, "One has sickness, and the other has no sickness. Which one do you belong to?"
I said, "You created me without a problem or sickness, that is where I belong".
He said, "Ok, lay here. There is no sickness there" and I Iay in the body with no sickness.
Corporal Yerimah Ojoh. Emmanuel TV testimony.
Amen.
I lay there and then woke up.
There was no pain in my body. I was very strong and agile.
I looked at all of this and started shouting in the hall.
All the soldiers came and asked what happened.
I said, "It's because of that prayer. God has done it!"
They were celebrating with me.
The soldier who was also being referred to Nigeria with me left alone.
That was in 2012, but you can see me here today.
I'm healthy. People do ask if Emmanuel TV testimonies are magic
or if Prophet T.B. Joshua truly is a man of God.
I am here today to let the world know, that "Yes. Indeed, he is a man of God".
Corporal Yerimah Ojoh. Emmanuel TV testimony.
Amen.
He had never known me before. He had never seen me before.
If somebody needs proof, see that my report is from Sudan.
This is a confirmation from the United Nations. It is not from Nigeria.
When I came back and shared what had happened with my wife,
she said that even if she had called to find out, I would have told her that there was no problem.
"Let us go and test because you're telling me it is a deadly disease."
I said, "It is a deadly disease. I wouldn't be here now".
She said, "Let us test". Then, I went to the medical hospital in Forty-four.
The tests were conducted and according to the report, instead of the level 80 where the devil wanted me to die,
Jesus has given me life and the new level is at 33. Amen.
The battallion I went with was number 33 and Jesus gave me the same healthy liver number of 33. Amen.
Which is a normal range?
That is the normal range. That is how it is supposed to be for a normal human being.
Amen.
The reason why I have not been able to come here all this while, to share this testimony,
is because there was a saying then, "Don't watch Emmanuel TV. Don't partner with them.
You're a pastor so don't mix with them".
After some time I started seeing senior pastors with Morning Stickers.
Corporal Yerimah Ojoh. Emmanuel TV testimony.
I started seeing them with Morning Stickers on their vehicles. Some even have Morning Water.
I thought to myself that I am not a senior pastor yet, I am just a baby.
Since I am a baby, let me share this testimony so that the world will know that
the disease that the devil says nobody can cure, God can cure it.
God can remove the old part and put in a new one. That was my case.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We give all the glory to God for this wonderful testimony.
Sir, you have said it all. In the light of what Jesus has done for you,
what is your advice to our viewers all over the world?
Emmanuel! My advice to the viewers all over world is:
Number one is for all the ministers.
Don't say anthing against yourselves; don't condemn yourselves.
This race is one that Jesus has called you to, you have to team up together to defeat satan.
He says something in John 15:15,
"Henceforth I call you not servants as a servant will not know what a master is doing.
I call you friends so that the things I do will be made known unto you".
So why can't we join hands together and support the Man of God and support each other
so that more miracles can happen every day.
Secondly, this is for my colleagues - wherever you are, even on the battle field, Jesus is there.
Always connect yourself with faith. Pray with the Man of God and you will receive your miracle.
Those on the sickbed, whether you are having the same problem that "that man" was having then
because he's no longer here now, a new person is here.
If you're having the same problem that "that man" was having then, connect your faith wherever you are
with the Man of God today because he will pray for you and you will receive your own miracle
and God will see you through, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!